Guide to the System Development Foundation (Palo Alto, Calif.) Records, 1957-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series 3. Financial Files
  - Subseries A. Grant finances
    - Subsubseries 2. Grant payment files
      - University of California at San Diego, G337a, G337b, G337c (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - University of California at San Diego, G351a, G351b (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - University of California at San Diego, G359a, G359b, G359d (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - University of California at San Diego, G675a, G675b. G675c (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - University of California at San Francisco, G550a, G550b, G550c (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - University of California at San Francisco, G892a, G892b (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - University of Chicago, G55a, G55c (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - University of Chicago, G357 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - University of Chicago, G763 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - University of Delaware, G301 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - University of Delaware, G403 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - University of Detroit, G677 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, G592 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - University of Kansas, G565 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - University of Manchester, G458 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - University of Massachusetts at Amherst, G626c, G626d (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - University of Massachusetts at Amherst, G633a, G633b, G633c (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - University of Massachusetts at Amherst, G650a, G650b, G650c (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - University of Michigan, G314a (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - University of Michigan, G524a, G524b (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - University of Oregon, G57a, G57b (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - University of Pennsylvania, G13a, G13b, G13c, G13e (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - University of Pennsylvania, G277 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - University of Pennsylvania, G590a, G590c (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - University of Pittsburgh, G687 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - University of Rochester, G481 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - University of Southern California, G15a, G15b, G15c (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - University of Southern California, G228 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - University of Southern California, G229 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - University of Texas at Austin, G626a, G626b (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - University of Utah, G348a, G348b, G348c, G348d (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - University of Utah, G456 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - University of Wisconsin at Madison, G492a, G492b, G492c (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - University of Wisconsin at Madison, G492d, G492e (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Whitehead University, G612b (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Yale University, G344 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Subsubseries 3. Financial review of files
      - Financial Review of Proposals, Board Material (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G004 - G057 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G136 - G285 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G303 - G389 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G403 - G492d (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G550c - G590c (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G612 - G675B (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G809 - G893 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, G910 - G969B (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Financial Review of Proposals, Symposium Grants (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Subsubseries 4. Case files
      - G004. Computation of Terminating Grant (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - G285B. Computuation of Grant Revision, 1985. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - G327. Administrative Review (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - G359. Unrestricted Grant (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - G460 (CSLI). Financial Policy: Interest on grants, 1983-1985. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - G460 (CSLI), Case File, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - G460 (CSLI), $2,700,00 grant. Case file 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - MIT Overhead file (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Subsubseries 5. Unexpended balance files
      - Unexpended balances. Working file, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Subsubseries 6. Grant summary and reconciliation files
      - Grants made, summary reports, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Grants made and amounts unpaid, "Huddleson list," Mar. 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Grants made, summary reports, Jan. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Grants made, summary reports, March 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Grants made, summary reports, Jun. - Jul. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Jun. 30, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Sep 30, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Dec. 31, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Mar. 31, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, May 31, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Jun. 30, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Sep. 30, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Dec. 31, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Mar. 31, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Jun. 30, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Sep. 30, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Dec. 31, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Mar. 31, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Jun. 30, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Sep. 30, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Dec. 30, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Mar. 30, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Grant reconciliation reports, Jun. 30, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Subsubseries 7. Miscellaneous grant reports
      - Grants approved, Dec. 1981 - Aug. 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Discretionary grants made 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous grant payment records, 1982 - 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Proposal Score Sheets (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Grant Budget database (Drafts) (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Grant lists, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B. Accounting
    Subseries B contains accounting documentation such as ledgers, chart of accounts, procedural files, cash flow projections, and termination models. Accounts payable records will be retained for 10 years and will be examined again for possible inclusion in the collection before they are discarded after December 31, 1998. Banking matters are filed in Subseries C.
    - Subsubseries 1. Administrative matters
      - Accounting Manual (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - SDF Policy and Plans (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Trustee Payment Procedure (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Financial Projects (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Contributions, gifts, grants, etc. 1974 - 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Expenses and temporary space ant SRI, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Property account analysis (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Anderson v. SDC Lawsuit (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Subsubseries 2. Chart of Accounts
      - Chart of accounts, c. 1982 - Mar. 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Chart of accounts, Jun. 1984 - Apr. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Budgets, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Budget Working File, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Subsubseries 3. Ledgers
      - General Ledger 1974-1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Journals, Jul 1, 1980 - Jun. 30, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Coluonnar Book, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Cash Disbursement General Ledger, FY 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Cash Disbursement General Ledger, FY 1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Ledgers: Journal Entries, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Cash Disbursements General Ledger, FY 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Cash Disbursement General Ledger, FY 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Cash Disbursement General Ledger, FY 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - General Ledger, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Cash Disbursement Budget vs. Actual Reports, Dec. 1, 1985 - Jun. 30, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Subsubseries 4. Cash flow
      - Ten Years Projections (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Oct. 31, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Jan. 31, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Apr. 30, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Cash Flow Projections, May 31, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Aug. 31, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Dec. 31, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Dec. 31, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Mar. 31, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Jun. 30, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Cash Flow Projections, Sep. 30, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Cash Flow Analysis, Dec. 31, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Cash Flow Analysis, Mar. 31, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Cash Flow Analysis, Jun. 30, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Cash Flow Analysis, Sep. 30, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Cash Flow Analysis, Dec. 31, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Cash Flow Analysis, Mar. 31, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Matched Maturities, Dec. 31, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Matched Maturities, Sep. 30, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Matched Maturities, Mar. 31, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Matched Maturities, Jun. 30, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Spending Pattern Projections, Jul. 1, 1984 - Sep. 30, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Operating Expense Analysis, 1981 - 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Termination Model Memo (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Termination Model, Mar. 31, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Termination Model, Sep. 30, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Termination Model, Dec. 31, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Termination Model, Mar. 31, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Termination Model, Jun. 30, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Termination Model, Sep. 30, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Termination Model, Mar. 31, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Accounting Principles and Reporting Practices for Certain Nonprofit Organizations, Dec. 31, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Subsubseries 5. Treasurer's reports
      - Treasurer's Report, Nov. 30, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Treasurer's Report, Feb. 28, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Treasurer's Report, Apr. 30, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Treasurer's Report, Jul. 31, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Treasurer's Report, Oct. 31, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Treasurer's Report, Jan. 31, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Treasurer's Report, Apr. 30, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Treasurer's Report, Jul. 31, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Treasurer's Report, Oct. 31, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Treasurer's Report, Dec. 31, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Treasurer's Report, Mar. 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Treasurer's Report, Jun. 30, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Treasurer's Report, Sep. 30, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Treasurer's Report, Dec. 12, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Treasurer's Report, Mar. 31, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Treasurer's Report, Jun. 30, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Treasurer's Report, Sep. 30, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Treasurer's Report, Dec. 31, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Treasurer's Report, Mar. 31, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Treasurer's Report,Jun. 30, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Treasurer's Report, Sep. 30, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Treasurer's Report, Dec. 31, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Treasurer's Report, Mar. 31, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Treasurer's Report, Jun. 30, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Treasurer's Report, Sep. 30, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Treasurer's Report, Dec. 31, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Treasurer's Report, Mar. 31, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Revised Treasurer's Report: Notes (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Subsubseries 6. Audits
      - SDC Report and Financial Statements, 1963, 1964, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - SDC Report and Financial Statements, 1969-1973, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - SDC Audit and Accounting: #11970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - SDC Audit and Accounting: #21970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - SDC Audit and Accounting: #31970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - SDC Audit and Accounting: #41970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Touche Ross Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Touche Ross Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Touche Ross Dates (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Touche Ross Technical Issues (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Touche Ross Adjustments and Reclassifications (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Audit Working Papers, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Audit Working Papers, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Touche Ross: Audit Reports1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Return from Inception:Jun. 30, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Return from Inception:Jun. 30, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Return from Inception:Jun. 30, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Return from Inception:Jun. 30, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Return from Inception:Jun. 30, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Investment Policy (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Investment Responsibilities (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Investment Objectives (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Planning Under the 1981 Economic Recovery Tax Act (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Investment Cushion (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Duration of Foundation (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Closing Matters, Jun. - Oct. 1988 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Allocation Report,Mar. 1982 - Feb. 1988 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Subseries C. Investments
    Subject files dealing with investments and investment policies of the Foundation are contained in subseries C. Since the majority of the banking files reflect the Foundation's investments, all banking records have been filed here. Cancelled checks, deposit slips and bank statements will be retained for 20 years and will be examined again for possible inclusion in the collection before they are destroyed after December 31, 2008.
    - Subsubseries 1. Policies and Administration
      - Investment Management Agreements (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 2. Investment Committee
      - Investment Committee (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Subsubseries 3. Investment Advisor's files
      - Investment Advisors (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Kennedy, Roger: Correspondence 1981 - 1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Kennedy, Roger: Report Preferences (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Moran, Lee: Correspondence 1981 - 1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Bond Portfolio Proposals (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Subsubseries 4. Security Pacific National Bank files
      - Scudder Documents (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Scudder Prospectuses and Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Check Signers and Expanded Check Signers (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - SPNB Correspondence, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - SPNB Correspondence, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - SPNB Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Security Pacific Correspondence, 1983 - 1987 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Subsubseries 5. Thorndike, Doran, Paine, & Lewis files
      - Thorndike Proposal (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Thorndike Transition (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Thorndike Contract (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Thorndike Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Thorndike Review Letters, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Thorndike Trades, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Bond Trade Problem, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Subsubseries 6. Well Fargo files
      - Wells Fargo Contract (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Wells Fargo Correspondence, 1981-1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Securities Lending Proposals (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Wells Fargo Index Fund Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Wells Fargo Index Fund Annual Statements, 1982 and 1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Bond Performance Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Wells Fargo Trades, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Subseries D. Taxes
    Subseries D contains local, state and federal tax returns and documentation relating to SDF's relationship with the IRS. Payroll and whithholding tax information and tax preparation materials will be retained for six years and will be examined again for possible inclusion in the collection before they are destroyed after December 31, 1994.
    - Subsubseries 1. Miscellaneous tax matters
      - Miscellaneous Tax Correspondence and Memo (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Business Property Statements, 1982-1986, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Property tax Exemption (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Statement by Domestic NonProfit Corporation (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Subsubseries 2. Tax audits
      - Audit Materials, Mar.-Apr. 1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Audit Materials, May 1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Subsubseries 3. Tax returns
      - Registry of Charitable Trust, FYE 6/30/70, 6/30/71 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Registry of Charitable Trust, FYE 6/30/72, 6/30/73, 6/30/74 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Registry of Charitable Trust, FYE 6/30/75, 6/30/76, 6/30/77 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Registry of Charitable Trust, FYE 6/30/78, 6/30/79, 6/30/80 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Annual Report of Private Foundation to IRS, FYE 6/30/72 - 6/30/75 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Annual Report of Private Foundation to IRS, FYE 6/30/76 - 6/30/79 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - State Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/57 - 6/30/64 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - State Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/65 - 6/30/69 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - State Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/70 - 6/30/72 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - State Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/73 - 6/30/75 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - State Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/76 - 6/30/81 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Federal Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/57 - 6/30/65 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Federal Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/66 - 6/30/71 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Federal Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/80 - 6/30/82 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Income Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/83 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Income Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/84 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Income Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/85 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Income Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/86 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Income Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/87 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Income Tax Returns, FYE 6/30/88 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Subsubseries 4. Liquidation tax form
      - Liquidation Tax Form, Aug. 25, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Series 4. Administrative Files
  This series contains the administrative files of SDF. General correspondence, files for special projects, office operation records and personnel files are included.
  - Subseries A. Correspondence
    This subseries contains chronological correspondence files, brief subject files of correspondence, and daily logs. These logs were maintained only briefly but provide a complete overview of the activities of the Foundation for that time period. Correspondence files were weeded, and confidential documents related to personnel matters were restricted or destroyed following recommended records retention guidelines. In addition, some correspondence regarding insurance and pension plans was moved to Subseries D, and tax and investment correspondence was removed to Series III.
    - Subsubseries 1. Chronological files
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jun. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jul. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Aug. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Sep. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Oct. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Nov. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Dec. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jan. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Feb. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Mar. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Apr. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Chronological correspondence file, May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jun. 28-30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jun. 1-25, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jul. 7-29, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jul. 1-6, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Aug. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Sep. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Oct. 18-28, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Oct. 1-14, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Nov. 12-29, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Nov. 1-10, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Dec. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jan. 18-28, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jan. 1-17, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Feb. 23-28, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Feb. 1-22, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Mar. 18-31, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Mar. 1-16, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Apr. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Chronological correspondence file, May 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jun. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jul. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Aug. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Sep. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Oct. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Nov. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Dec. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jan. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Feb. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Mar. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Apr. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Chronological correspondence file, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jun. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jul. 19-31, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jul. 2-18, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Aug. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Sep. 18-28, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Sep. 6-13, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Oct. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Nov. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Dec. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Jan. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Feb. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Mar. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Chronological correspondence file, Apr. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)